

Matthew Montoya

Full Stack Web Developer



Summary



I am a full-stack developer with a background in retail management who is passionate about meeting client's needs, problem solving, and CSS! Based on my experience as a team leader, I look forward to working with teams to build interactive and responsive applications!



Experience

2018-03 -2018-06

Web Development Immersive

General Assembly

Completed a 12- week, 600+ hour Web Development Immersive program in which I developed and deployed three full-stack applications while using the industries best practices. Two of the projects were done independently and one was developed in a team environment.

The full-stack projects go as follows:

<u>JamMate</u>

JamMate is a full stack application created with the intention of allowing authenticated users to find local artists based on the type of instrument that they play and their genre.

A user is able to create their listing of instruments and view everyone's listings.

Sserpdrow

Team project in association with Patrick O'Day and Sparrow Rubin in which we developed a full-stack application that would allow authenticated users to create pages and blog posts. This application was created with using Express.js and MongoDB.

Pro[Stock] Systems

Pro[Stock] Systems is a full-stack application developed with the intention of allowing authenticated users to be able to keep track of their personal inventory. As inventory levels change, the user is able to updated or delete inventory based on their needs.

2014-07 -2018-03

Assistant Manager

<u>Tumi</u>

- Select, train, coach, and develop a team.
- Monitor, maintain, and verify inventory accuracy and product levels.
- · Manage shipments and ensuring timely delivery.
- Strive to drive sales to meet monthly and yearly goals.
- Meticulously reconcile daily receipts and bank deposits.
- Create weekly schedules and audit payroll.



Education

2018-03 -2018-06

General Assembly

Web Development Immersive

2012 -2014

University of Massachusetts Boston

Iberian and Latin American Studies



Software

♠ AT

ATOM Editor



Advanced

Sublime Editor



Address

320 Adams Street

Apt 204

Lowell, MA 01854

Phone

(978) 930.3721

E-mail

mattrmontoya@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/mattrmontoya

GitHub

github.com/Matty-Montoya

Porfolio

mmontoya.me



Skills

HTML

Bootstrap

CSS / SASS

Javascript

Node.js Ember.js

JQuery

Ruby

Ruby on Rails

MongoDB

Mongoose

Handlebars

PostgreSQL

Git/Github



Languages

English



Spanish

